Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of War and Peace Movements Serials TAM.757
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of War and Peace Movements Serials
1914-2009
1970-1989
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
American Friends Service Committee
TAM.757
11 Linear Feet in 18 manuscript boxes and 13 flat boxes
The Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of War and Peace Movements Serials contains over 500 titles on war, peace movements, disarmament, and related topics in the 20th century published in the United States, Asia, Europe, South America, Cuba, and Canada. The collection dates between 1914 and 2009, with the bulk of the material dating from the 1970s through 1980s.
Conditions Governing Access
Open to users without restriction.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Due to the fragile nature of certain original materials, researchers may be required to consult microfilm copies, preservation photocopies, or digital images of material in this collection.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This collection combines serials relating to war and peace movements drawn from two discrete groups of material held by the Tamiment Library. The first was a partially inventoried backlog of serials, received by the library through donations, subscriptions, and in archival collections. The second group consisted of around 1,700 serials, newspapers, and magazines, organized by title as an artificial collection, referred to as Periodicals.001 or Boxed Newspapers. This material was combined, inventoried, and arranged and described in subject-based categories in 2017. The accession number related to this collection is 2017.049.
Scope and Contents
The Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of War and Peace Movements Serials contains over 500 titles on war, peace movements, disarmament, and related topics in the 20th century published in the United States (US), Asia, Europe, South America, Cuba, and Canada. The collection dates between 1914 and 2009, with the bulk of the material dating from the 1970s through 1980s. Topics related to war include the Vietnam War, World War I, World War II, the Cold War, the Spanish Civil War, conflicts in the Middle East and South and Central America throughout the 20th century, and the threat of nuclear war. Topics related to peace movements include protest movements, especially of the Vietnam War; nuclear disarmament; and conscientious objection. A number of titles are related to organizations comprised of students, women, veterans, or religious groups focused on a particular peace or protest movement, including the American Friends Service Committee.
Arrangement
Serials in this collection are arranged alphabetically by title.
Vietnam War, 1961-1975 -- Periodicals.; Vietnam War, 1961-1975 -- Protest movements.; Nuclear disarmament.; Nuclear warfare -- History -- 20th century.; Peace movements -- United States.; Vietnam War, 1961-1975 -- Veterans -- United States.; Veterans -- Political activity -- United States.; Anti-war demonstrations.; War resistance movements -- United States.
- 1st Casualty: Vietnam Veterans Against the War, New York, NY, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- A Black Woman Speaks...: American Women for Peace, New York, NY, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- A Call to Students and Youth for a National Day of No Business as Usual: NBAU, San Francisco, CA, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- A Four-Year Bummer (formerly Harass the Brass): Champaign, IL, 1969-1971 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- A Handbook on the War in Asia: Students, Faculty, and Staff, University of California, Berkeley, Berkeley, CA, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- A New World Rising: A New World Rising, Providence, RI, Undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
- A Peace Plan for Central America: Intentional Futures Inc., Oak Beach, NY, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- A Statement from Veterans to Youth: Vietnam Veterans United to Prevent World War III, New York, NY, Undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
- A Vision of America at Peace: Ground Zero/Vision, Berkeley, CA, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- ABC Doble Diario de la Guerra Civil: Prensa Espanola, Madrid, Spain, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 7-9)
- About Face!: The U.S. Servicemen's Fund, New York, NY, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Across Frontiers: Ztangi Press, Berkeley, CA, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Across the Lines: Seeds of Peace, San Francisco, CA, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- ACT: RITA, Paris, France, 1968-1970 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Action Bulletin: Livermore Action Group, Berkeley, CA, Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Action Newsletter: Peace Center of Bergen County, Teaneck, NJ, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Action Report: Peace Action / Peace Action Education Fund, Washington, DC, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Activist: Buffalo Youth Against War and Fascism, Buffalo, NY, 1969-1971 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- ACTivist: ACT for Disarmament, Toronto, Ontario, 1989-1995 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Activist: United Committee Against the War, Berkeley, CA, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Aegis: Nurses Alliance for the Prevention of Nuclear War, Chestnut Hill, MA, 1982-1988 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Ahimsa: Students for Peace / Eastern Connecticut State College, Willimantic, CT, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Alabama Nuclear Freeze Campaign: Alabama Nuclear Freeze Campaign, Birmingham, AL, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Alert: Performing Artists for Nuclear Disarmament, New York, NY, Undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
- All Ways Free: Rainbow Peace Project Foundation, Madison, WI, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Ally: A Newspaper for Servicemen: The Ally, Berkeley, CA, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Amistad Friendship: Amistad/Friendship, Vancouver, BC, Canada, 1993-1995 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- An International Commission on Peaceful Co-Existence (A Report): The Vedanta Movement, Bath, UK, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Annual Report - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace: The Endowment, New York, NY, 1948-1949 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Another Mother for Peace: Another Mother for Peace, Beverly Hills, CA, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Anti Kriegs Info: Frankfurt, Germany, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Anti-War Activist: The Anti-War Activist, New York, NY, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Anti-Warrior: Anti-Warrior, Berkeley, CA, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Antioch Notes: Antioch College, Yellow Springs, OH, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Armistice News: Armistice, Seattle, WA, 1981-1984 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Army Times: Army Times Publishing Company, Washington, DC, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Associates Newsletter: Global Education Associates, East Orange, NJ, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Atlanta Workshop in NonViolence Newsletter: Atlanta Workshop in NonViolence, Atlanta, GA, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Atlas: Aspen Publishing Company, New York, NY, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Azione Nonviolenta: Rivista mensile del Movimento Nonviolento fondata da Aldo Capitini nel 1964: Movimento Nonviolento, Verona, Italy, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- B.A.N.G. Notes: Brooklyn Anti-Nuclear Group, Brooklyn, NY, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- B.E.F. Crusader: Walter W. Waters, New York, NY, 1932 (Box Shared Tamiment 052, Folder 9)
- Bailly Alliance News: Bailly Alliance, Chesterton, Indiana, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Baltimore Jobs wih Peace: Baltimore Jobs with Peace, Baltimore, MD, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Baptist Peacemaker: Baptist Peace Fellowship of North America, Memphis, TN, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Because People Matter: Sacramento Community for Peace & Justice, Sacramento, CA, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Bentre: NYU Liberation Front, New York, NY, Undated (Box 19, Folder 17, Box 27, Folder 4)
- Between the Lines: Sacramento Peace Center, Sacramento, CA, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Big Muddy Gazette: Muddy Tribe and Friends, Carbondale, IL, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Black Man's Stake in Vietnam: Black Panther Party, Undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Black Vet: Black Veterans for Social Justice, Inc., Brooklyn, NY, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Black Veteran Communicator: Black Veterans for Social Justice, Brooklyn, NY, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 21-22)
- Blue Book Series: The Riverside Church Disarmament Program, New York, NY, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Blueprint for Social Justice: Institute of Human Relations, Loyola University, New Orleans, LA, 1989-1997 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Boekovski Berichten: Stichting Comite Vladimir Boekovski, Amsterdam, Holland, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Boletin de Solidaridad Argentina con Vietnam: Buenos Aires, Argentina, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Books that Make a Difference: War Resisters League Literature List: War Resisters League, New York, NY, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Breaking Point: Union of Concerned Scientists, Cambridge, MA, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Briefing Paper: National Network of Indochina Activists, New York, NY, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Briefing Paper: Union of Concerned Scientists, Cambridge, MA, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Brooklyn Heights SANE/FREEZE Newsletter: Brooklyn Heights SANE/FREEZE, Brooklyn, NY, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Build the Anti-Imperialist Veterans Movement: Revolutionary Union, Chicago, IL, Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Bulletin: Mobilization for Survival, Philadelphia, PA, 1985-1987 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Bulletin d'Information Publie par le Collectif Intersyndical d'Action pour la Paix au Viet Nam: Collectif Intersyndical d'Action pour la Paix au Viet Nam, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Bulletin of the South Vietnam National Front for Liberation: South Vietnam Liberation Press Agency, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Bulletin of the World Council of Peace: World Council of Peace, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Burning Issues Newsletter: Burning Issues, New York, NY, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- C.I.O. and National Defense: American Council on Public Affairs, Washington, DC, Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
- California Military Monitor: Pacific Studies Center, Mountain View, CA, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Cambodia-News in Brief: Office of Information of the National United Front of Kampuchea, Peking, China, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 14-17)
- CAMP News: CAMP News, Chicago, IL, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Campaign Notes: Campaign for the Second UN Special Session on Disarmament, New York, NY, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Campaign Report: National Jobs With Peace Campaign, Boston, MA, 1992-1994 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Carpetbag Express, Undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
- CCCO's News Notes: CCCO, Philadelphia, PA, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Ce Qu'il Faut Dire: Bimensuel de Libre Culture et D'Action Pacifiste, Paris, France, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Cease Fire Special: Indochina Peace Campaign, Montclair, NJ, Undated (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Center Review: Center for Psychological Studies in the Nuclear Age, Cambridge, MA, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Change-Links: Progressive Newspaper & Community Calendar: Change-Links, Hollywood, CA, Undated (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Channeling Memo: American Friends Service Committee, Inc., Cambridge, MA, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Chessman II: Short Times Staff, Columbia, SC, Undated (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Chiapas Times: Vermont Chiapas Action Network, Burlington, VT, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- CIAC: Centro de Informacion del Consejo Mundial de la Paz para America y el Caribe, Havana, Cuba, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Citizen Soldier: Citizen Soldier, New York, NY, 1982-1984 (Box 4, Folder 10, Box 19, Folder 27)
- Citizens First, Veterans Second: American Veterans Committee, Inc., Washington, DC, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Civil Disobedience Action Training Handbook: Coalition for a Non-Nuclear World, Washington, DC, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Coalition Update: Coalition for a Nuclear-Free Harbor, New York, NY, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Column Left: Veterans Club at the University of Buffalo, Buffalo, NY, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Combat Ethnic Weapons: Coalition Opposed to Medical and Biological Attack, San Francisco, CA, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Committee for Nonviolent Action Bulletin: Committee for Nonviolent Action, New York, NY, 1961-1967 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Committee of Returned Volunteers: Committee of Returned Volunteers, New York, NY, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Community: Syracuse Peace Council, Syracuse, NY, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Community Meeting About the War: Mission Hill Vietnam, n.p., circa 1960s (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Community Peace Action Bulletin: American Friends Service Committee, New York, NY, 1971-1973 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Con$cience & Military Tax Campaign-U.S.: Con$cience & Military Tax Campaign-U.S., Bellport, NY, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Confinee Says: Camp Pendleton, Camp Pendleton, CA, Undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Congressional Magazine: United States Commission for Enduring Peace, Washington, DC, 1916 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Congressman Vito Marcantonio speaks out Against This War: American Peace Mobilization, New York, NY, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Connections: Peace and Justice Network of San Joaquin County, Stockton, CA, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Conscientious Objection or Nonregistration: Making a Choice: National Resistance Committee, San Francisco, CA, Undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Conscientious Objector: Conscientious Objector, New York, NY, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- COR Report: Committee of Responsibility for War-Burned and War-Injured Vietnamese Children, New York, NY, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- CTA Reports: Consider the Alternatives, Philadelphia, PA, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Current Issues combined with Disarmament News: Fellowship of Reconciliation, Nyack, NY, Undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
- CVR/NY: Committee of Returned Volunteers, New York, NY, Undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Daily News: B.A.N.G. (Brooklyn Anti-Nuclear Group), Brooklyn, NY, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Dancers for Disarmament Newsletter: Communications Committee, New York, NY, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Death Ship Times: The Defense Committee, Charleston, SC, 1974 (Box Shared Tamiment 052, Folder 10)
- Demilitarized Zones: East River Anthology, Perkasie, PA, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Desert Voices: Nevada Desert Experience, Las Vegas, NV, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Desobeissance Civile: Ed du groupe THOREAU, Quebec, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Die Glocke vom Ettersberg: Willy Schmidt, Frankfurt, Germany, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Die Weltwoche, 1942 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Dimensions: Anti-Defamation League, New York, NY, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Disarmament Action Guide: Coalition for a New Foreign and Military Policy, Washington, DC, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Disarmament Campaigns: Anna Paulownaplein, The Hague, Netherlands, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Disarmament News: World Disarmament Campaign, Portsmouth, NH, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 31, Box 20, Folder 5)
- Disarming Notes: Riverside Church Disarmament Program, New York, NY, 1987 (Box Shared Tamiment 052, Folder 11)
- Disarmament Times: NGO Committtee on Disarmament, Inc., New York, NY, 1981-1997 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Disarming Notes: Riverside Church Disarmament Program, New York, NY, 1979-1992 (Box 4, Folder 33, Box 18, Folder 2)
- DMZ: Vietnam Veterans Against the War - Clarence Fitch Chapter, Brooklyn, NY, 1987-1994 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Documentary to Reveal Collaboration Between B'nai B'rith and Nazis: The LaRouche Campaign, New York, NY, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Dove: The Dove, Lawrence, KS, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Draft Action News: Independent Student Union, New York, NY, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Draft Law and Antiwar Protests: Draft Law Group, Yale Law School, Hartford, CT, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Draft Registration is No Joke!: National Resistance Committee, San Francisco, CA, Undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Drinking Gourd: Nashua Peace Center, Nashua, NH, 1991-1995 (Box 5, Folder 6-9)
- East Side Newsletter: Nuclear Weapons Freeze Campaign, New York, NY, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- ECO: Friends of the Earth, New York, NY, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- El Pensador: CNT-AIT de Andorra/Acrata "El Sembrador", Andorra, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- End European Nuclear Disarmament Bulletin, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Entrüstet euch: wir wollen leben: Analysen zur atomaren Bedrohung: Wege zum Frieden: Die Grunen, Bonn, Germany, Undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Erasmian Outlook, 1934 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Ergo/Downdraft: Committee for Peace/ End the Draft Committee, Brooklyn, NY, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- European Security: International Meeting of Journalists: Interpress Publishers, Warsaw, Poland, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Europeans Cry "No!": Riverside Church Disarmament Program, New York, NY, Undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Every GI Is a P.O.W.: GI's from Fort Ord, Monterey, CA, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Fat Albert's Death Ship Times: The Defense Committee, North Charleston, SC, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Felix Greene Reports: Voluntary Labour/The Black Mountain Press, Corinth, VT, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Fight Back!: G.I. Rights and Information Center, Long Beach, CA, Undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Fightback: All-People's Congress/People's Anti-War Mobilization, New York, NY, 1990 (Box Shared Tamiment 052, Folder 12)
- Fighting Back: All-Peoples Congress / People's Anti-War Mobilization, New York, NY, 1985-1990 (Box 20, Folder 9-11)
- For Peace & Solidarity: Peace and Solidarity Project, Oakland, CA, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 12-13, Box 6, Folder 3)
- For-cast: Fellowship of Reconciliation, Philadelphia, PA, 1961-1962 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Foreign-Born Americans and the War: American Committee for Protection of Foreign Born, New York, NY, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- FORsooth: Louisville Chapter of the Fellowship of Reconciliation, Louisville, KY, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Forward: League for Democratic Control, Boston, MA, 1919 (Box Shared Tamiment 063, Folder 12)
- Freedom and Peace Free Press: Freedom & Peace Party, New York, NY, 1969-1972 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Freeze Focus: The Nuclear Weapons Freeze Campaign, St. Louis, MO, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Friedenszeitung: Schweizerischer Friedensrat, Zurich, Switzerland, 1986-1996 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Friendshipment: People to People Aid to Vietnam/Faculty Press, Inc., New York, NY, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 9, Box Shared Tamiment 052, Folder 13)
- Friendshipment: Friendshipment, New York, NY, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- friZ: redakation friZ, Zurich, Switzerland, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Fun Travel Adventure (FTA): Louisville, KY, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Future: Future, Denver, CO, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Gadfly: Postcrypt Press, New York, NY, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Gensuikin News: Japan Congress Against Atomic and Hydrogen Bombs, Tokyo, Japan, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Gifts for Peace and Freedom WILPF 1987 Catalog: Women's International League for Peace and Freedom, Philadelphia, PA (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Global reality ... from vision to reality: an international women's conference newsletter: Peacemakers, Inc., Dallas, TX, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Godforsaken City: Henry H. Klein, New York, NY, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Government's Attempted Murder of Brian Wilson: Vietnam Veterans United to Prevent WWIII, New York, NY, Undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Graffiti: G.I.s for G.I.s, Heidelberg, Germany, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 19, Box 27, Folder 12)
- Grassroots Action Newsletter: NY SANE Council, New York, NY, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Grassroots Fundraising Handbook: Women's International League for Peace & Freedom, Philadelphia, PA, Undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Graswurzelrevolution: Fur eine Gewaltfreie, Herrschaftslose Gesellschaft: Graswurzelrevolution, Hamburg, Germany, Undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Greater Boston Campaign Update: Campaign for the Second UN Special Session on Disarmament, Boston, MA, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Greetings to the Veterans of the Spanish Civil War: Julia Reichert / Jim Klein, Dayton, OH, Undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Grenzen der Gewalt: Indochina Peace Campaign, Karlsbad, Germany, 1934 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Ground Zero: Ground Zero Center for Nonviolent Action, Poulsbo, WA, 1979-1987 (Box 6, Folder 26, Box 20, Folder 16)
- Groupe Thoreau: Librairie Alternative, Montreal, Quebec, Undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Gulf War Notes: Black Cat Press, New York, NY, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Gung-Ho: Charlton Publications, Inc., Derby, CT, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Harc!: American Association of Democratic Hungarians, New York, NY, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Health Workers' Declaration on the Arms Race and the Threat of Nuclear War: World Conference on Health Workers and Social Well-Being, Health and Peace, Moscow, Russia, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Heights Peaceletter: Brooklyn Heights Peace Action, Brooklyn, NY, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- High Frontier: Daniel O. Graham, Washington, DC, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- High School Student Mobilizer: National Student Mobilization Committee, New York, NY, Undated (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Hoa Binh: Colorado Vietnam Veterans Against the War, Denver, CO, Undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Holocaust Oral History Manual: Center for Holocaust Studies, New York, NY, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Hotline: Common Cause Nuclear Arms Alert Network, Washington, DC, 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Houston Peace News: Houston Peace News, Houston, TX, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- How the United States Got Involved in Vietnam: Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions of the Fund for the Republic, Inc., Santa Barbara, CA, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- ICV Newsletter: Independent Committee on Vietnam of Columbia University, New York, NY, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Impeachment - Make It Happen: American Civil Liberties Union, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- In Defense of Peace: Committee of the world congress of the defenders of peace, Paris, France, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- In Passing: A Walk to Moscow, Seattle, WA, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- In the Aftermath of the Holocaust: Three Generations Speak: The Moriah School of Englewood, Englewood, NJ, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Indo-China and World Peace: New Century Publishers, New York, NY, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Indo-China Newsletter: World Peace Council, Athens, Greece, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Indochina Bulletin: Asia Information Group, Berkeley, CA, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 20-22)
- Indochina Bulletin: Asia Information Group, Syracuse, NY, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Indochina Focal Point: Indochina Peace Campaign, Santa Monica, CA, 1973-1975 (Box 7, Folder 3-4, Box 17)
- Indochina Information from Vermont: Vermont, Undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Indochina Interchange: U.S.-Indochina Reconciliation Project of the Fund for Reconciliation and Development, New York, NY, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Indochina Peace Campaign Newsletter: Indochina Peace Campaign, Montclair, NJ, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Indochina Program Newsletter: American Friends Service Committee, Inc., Philadelphia, PA, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Indochina Summer News Flash: American Friends Service Committee, Inc., Philadelphia, PA, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Indochina: In Support of the Indochinese People: Gutter Press, London, UK, 1973-1975 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- INFACT Nuclear Weaponmakers Campaign Update: INFACT National Field Campaign Office, South Pasadena, CA, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Information: Peace Council of the German Democratic Republic, Berlin, Germany, 1973-1989 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Information about Nazi-Germany: American Committee for Anti-Nazi Literature, New York, NY, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Information from the Peace Movement of the German Democratic Republic: Peace Council of the German Democratic Republic, Berlin, Germany, 1964-1979 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Informations-Dienst Fur Soldaten: Jugendmagazin Elan, Dortmund, Germany, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Inner City Light: Universal Cycle Company, New York, NY, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- International Accidental Nuclear War Prevention Newsletter: Nuclear Age Peace Foundation, Santa Barbara, CA, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 16)